George and Ira Gershwin Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music (Box 1-63)
  - Music from Shows (Box 1-47)
    - Tell me more [1925] (Box 39-41)
      - In Sardinia
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 9 p., No lyric; Includes encore (Box-folder 40/9)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 40/9)
      - Incidental
        - Copyist manuscript piano score; [2] p. (Box-folder 40/10)
      - Kenneth won the yachting race, Alternate title for "Finaletto, Act II, scene 1," Box-Folder 39/34
      - Kickin' the clouds away
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 16 p., No lyric; Emendations in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 40/11)
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 40/11)
      - Lady fair, Alternate title for "My fair lady," Box-Folder 40/15
      - Love is in the air
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p., No lyric (Box-folder 40/12)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 5 p., No lyric; Emendations in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 40/13)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [9] p., No lyric (Box-folder 40/13)
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 40/13)
      - Mr. and Mrs. Sipkin
        - 2 copyist manuscript piano-vocal scores; 8 p. ea., No lyric (Box-folder 40/14)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 10 p., No lyric; Emendations in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 40/14)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 18 p., No lyric; Emendations in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 40/14)
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 40/14)
      - Monty! Their only child, Alternate title for "Mr. and Mrs. Sipkin," Box-Folder 40/14
      - My fair lady
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [6] p., Emendations in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 40/15)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 18 p., Emendations in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 40/15)
        - Manuscript lead sheet; [2] p., Sketch material on p. [3] (Box-folder 40/15)
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 40/15)
      - Once
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of William Daly; [3] p., No lyric (Box-folder 40/16)
        - Manuscript piano score in the hand of Hilding Anderson; [3] p. (Box-folder 40/16)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [3] p. (Box-folder 40/16)
      - Opening, Act I, Alternate title for "Shopgirls and mannequins," Box-Folder 40/19
      - Opening, Act II, Alternate title for "Love is in the air," Box-Folder 40/12-13
      - Opening, Act II scene 3, See also "Ukelele lorelei," Box-Folder 41/1-3
        - Copyist manuscript piano score; [3] p. (Box-folder 40/17)
        - Manuscript sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 40/17)
      - Opening ensemble, Alternate title for "Shopgirls and mannequins," Box-Folder 40/19
      - Selection
        - Robert Russell Bennett holograph manuscript piano score; 23 p. (Box-folder 40/18)
      - Shopgirls and manequins
        - Copyist manuscript piano score; 13 p., Emendations in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 40/19)
        - 2 copyist manuscript piano parts; 18 p. ea. (Box-folder 40/19)
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 40/19)
      - Sole mio
        - Copyist manuscript piano score; [1] p. (Box-folder 40/20)
        - Manuscript piano sketch; [1] p., Music not by GG (Box-folder 40/20)
      - Specialty no. 1
        - Robert Russell Bennett holograph manuscript piano score; [2] p., Music not by GG (Box-folder 40/21)
      - Tell me more
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p., No lyric (Box-folder 40/22)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 1, 4 p., No lyric (Box-folder 40/23)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 1, 4 p., No lyric; Notes in an unidentified hand on p. [5] (Box-folder 40/23)
        - Copyist manuscript TTBB arrangement for men’s chorus; [2] p., No piano (Box-folder 40/23)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [3] p. (Box-folder 40/23)
      - Tell me more. Reprise
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [1, 3] p. (Box-folder 40/24)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 6 p., Emendations in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 40/24)
      - Three times a day
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p., Lyric and emendations in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 40/25)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 6 p., No lyric (Box-folder 40/25)
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 40/25)
      - Ukelele Lorelei
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p., Refrain (partial lyric) with realized chords for ukulele in an unidentified hand on p. [4] (Box-folder 41/1)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [10] p., No lyric; Piano introduction for "Opening, Act II, scene 3" on p. [1-2]; Encore music on p. [7-10] (Box-folder 41/2)
        - 2 copyist manuscript piano-vocal scores; [5] p. ea., No lyric (Box-folder 41/2)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 1, 10 p., Emendations in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 41/2)
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 41/2)
      - Ukelele Lorelei. Dance
        - GG holograph manuscript piano score; [3] p. (Box-folder 41/3)
      - Waltz
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal sketch; [3] p., No lyric (Box-folder 41/4)
      - When my oil well starts gush-gush-gushing, Alternate title for "Gushing," Box-Folder 39/5-40/2
      - When the Debbies go by
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p., No lyric; On p. [4] in an unidentified hand: Reprise, Tell me more (Box-folder 41/5)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p., No lyric; Emendations in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 41/5)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [1, 5] p., No lyric; Emendations in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 41/6)
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 41/6)
      - Where the delicatessen flows, Alternate title for "In Sardinia," Box-Folder 40/8-9
      - Why do I love you?
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; [1, 4] p., No lyric; Discarded sketch of opening on p. [2] (Box-folder 41/7)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 5 p., Emendations in an unidentified hand; Includes 4 bar introduction; Key of E minor (Box-folder 41/8)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 11 p., No lyric; Emendations in an unidentified hand; Includes encores on p. 6-11; Key of A flat major (Box-folder 41/8)
        - Copyist manuscript piano score; [3] p. (Box-folder 41/8)
        - Manuscript piano score; [1, 2] p., Encore music (Box-folder 41/8)
        - Photocopied sheet music (German) (Box-folder 41/8)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [3] p. (Box-folder 41/8)
      - Untitled
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [3] p., No lyric; Emendations in an unidentified hand; Vocal line crossed out; In caption: 15 B (Box-folder 41/9)
        - Copyist manuscript piano score; [1, 2] p., On cover: 15 B (Box-folder 41/9)
      - Run down sheet of copyist
        - Manuscript list; [1] p. (Box-folder 41/10)
    - That's a good girl [1928] (Box 41)
      - Before we were married
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 41/11)
      - Chirp chirp!
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 41/12)
      - Day after day
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 41/13)
      - Let yourself go!
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 41/14)
      - The one I'm looking for
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 41/15)
      - Sweet so-and-so
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 41/16)
      - There I'd settle down
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 41/17)
      - Weekend
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 41/18)
      - What to do?, Original title for "Whoopee," Box-Folder 41/19
      - Whoopee
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 41/19)
      - Why be good?
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 41/20)
      - Libretto title page
        - IG holograph manuscript; [1] p. (Box-folder 41/21)
      - Song synopsis
        - 2 IG holograph/typescript manuscripts; [1] p. ea. (Box-folder 41/22)
    - Tip toes [1925] (Box 41-45)
      - Finale, Act I
        - Typescript lyric sheets; 5 p. (Box-folder 41/23)
      - Finale, Act II
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [3] p. (Box-folder 41/24)
      - Florida, Alternate title for "Waiting for the train," Box-Folder 42/7-9
      - Gather-ye-rosebuds
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p., No lyric (Box-folder 41/25)
        - Photocopied copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p. (Box-folder 41/25)
        - Photocopied copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [5] p. (Box-folder 41/25)
        - IG holograph/typescript/photocopied lyric sheets; [3] p. (Box-folder 41/25)
      - Harbor of dreams
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 41/26)
      - The Harlem River chanty
        - GG holograph manuscript piano score; [3] p. (Box-folder 41/27)
        - GG holograph manuscript piano sketch; [2] p., In caption in the hand of IG: Part of Harlem River chanty (Box-folder 41/28)
        - 4 photocopied (ozalid) piano-vocal scores; 5 p. ea., 2 have IG holograph notes (Box-folder 41/29)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [7] p. (Box-folder 41/29)
      - It's a great little world
        - GG holograph manuscript piano score; 3 p. (Box-folder 41/30)
        - 2 copyist manuscript piano-vocal scores; 5 p. ea., One has emendations in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 41/31)
        - Manuscript/copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 1, 1 p., Incomplete, no lyric; Caption title in the hand of IG (Box-folder 41/31)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [3] p. (Box-folder 41/31)
      - Lady luck
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 41/32)
      - Life's too short to be blue
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 41/33)
      - Looking for a boy
        - GG holograph manuscript piano sketch; [1] p., Sketch of Vodka on p. [2] (Box-folder 41/34)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p., Lyric and emendations in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 41/35)
        - Photocopied sheet music (French version) (Box-folder 41/35)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [5] p. (Box-folder 41/35)
      - Nice baby!
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p., Emendations in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 41/36)
        - Photocopied fragment of a piano solo arrangement from the verso of “Delishious” arr.; [1] p., See "Delishious [arranged for piano solo]," Box-Folder 4/15 for the original (Box-folder 41/36)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [3] p. (Box-folder 41/36)
      - Nice baby! Come to Papa!, Alternate title for "Waiting for the train," Box-Folder 42/7-9
      - Nightie night
        - 2 copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p. ea., Emendations in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 41/37)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [6] p., One has corrections (Box-folder 41/37)
      - Opening, Act I, Alternate title for "Waiting for the train," Box-Folder 42/7-9
      - Opening, Act I, scene 2, Alternate title for "Lady luck," Box-Folder 41/32
      - Our little captain
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 41/38)
      - Selection
        - Copyist manuscript (with printed portions) piano score; 23 p., Arranged by Robert Russell Bennett; Emendations in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 42/1)
        - Sheet music (incomplete); [2] p., Arranged by Robert Russell Bennett; Emendations in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 42/1)
      - Sweet and low-down
        - 2 copyist manuscript piano-vocal scores; [4] p. ea., Emendations in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 42/2)
        - Photocopied sheet music (French) (Box-folder 42/2)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [3] p. (Box-folder 42/2)
      - That certain feeling
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [3] p., Partial lyric and emendations in an unidentified hand; Credit in the hand of IG (Box-folder 42/3)
        - Sheet music with corrections, Corrections in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 42/3)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [4] p. (Box-folder 42/3)
      - These charming people
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p., Emendations in an unidentified hand; Credit in the hand of IG (Box-folder 42/4)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [4] p. (Box-folder 42/4)
      - Tip toes
        - Photocopied piano-vocal score; [3] p., French and English lyrics; Laid in: Typescript letter from Louis Aborn to IG, 1976 July 27 (Box-folder 42/5)
        - Photocopied vocal part and lyric sheet; [1] p. ea., Laid in: Typescript letter from Louis Aborn to IG, 1976 June 2; Laid in: Typescript letter from Edgar Carter to Louis Aborn, 1976 June 11 (Box-folder 42/5)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 42/5)
      - Trombone specialty
        - GG holograph manuscript piano sketch; [1] p., Includes 8 bar exit; Drums part for "Tip toes" on p. [2] (Box-folder 42//6)
      - Waiting for the train
        - Photocopied copyist manuscript piano score; 4 p. (Box-folder 42/7)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 42/7)
        - Photocopied piano-vocal score; [6] p., French and English lyrics; Laid in: Typescript letter from Louis Aborn to IG, 1976 July 27 (Box-folder 42/8)
        - Photocopied lyric sheets; 2 p., Laid in: Typescript letter from Louis Aborn to IG, 1976 June 2; Laid in: Typescript letter from Edgar Carter to Louis Aborn, 1976 June 11 (Box-folder 42/9)
      - We, Typescript lyric sheets; 2 p. (Box-folder 42/10)
      - Weaken a bit
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets (Box-folder 42/11)
      - When do we dance?
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p., Lyric and emendations in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 42/12)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [5] p., Corrections in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 42/12)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [3] p. (Box-folder 42/12)
      - Miscellaneous/unidentified music
        - 4 items found with the Secaucus Tip Toes material (Box-folder 42/13)
      - Orchestral parts
        - Entr’acte
          - 14 parts (incomplete set) (Box-folder 42/14)
        - Entr’acte [variant]
          - 8 parts (incomplete set) (Box-folder 42/15)
        - Finale, Act I
          - 15 parts (incomplete set) (Box-folder 42/16)
        - Finale, Act II
          - 15 parts (Box-folder 42/17)
        - Finale, Act II [variant]
          - Piano part only (Box-folder 42/18)
        - It's a great little world
          - 17 parts, Cover title: Give in (Box-folder 42/19)
        - Lady luck
          - 15 parts (incomplete set) (Box-folder 42/20)
        - Looking for a boy
          - 17 parts (incomplete set) (Box-folder 43/1)
          - 27 printed parts (incomplete set) (Box-folder 43/2)
        - Looking for a boy. Reprise 11A/12
          - 14 parts (incomplete set) (Box-folder 43/3)
        - Looking for a boy. Reprise 13A-B-C
          - 15 parts (incomplete set) (Box-folder 43/4)
        - Looking for a boy. Reprise 14
          - 8 parts (trumpet and strings only) (Box-folder 43/5)
        - Lucky day
          - 10 printed parts with emendations, Published as part of George White's Scandals of 1926, perhaps interpolated in Tip toes (Box-folder 43/6)
        - Nice baby!
          - 16 parts (incomplete set) (Box-folder 43/7)
        - Nice baby! Come to Papa!, Alternate title for "Nice baby!," Box-Folder 43/7
        - Nice baby! Reprise
          - 14 parts (incomplete set) (Box-folder 43/8)
        - Nightie night
          - 11 parts (incomplete set A) (Box-folder 43/9)
          - 14 parts (incomplete set B) (Box-folder 43/10)
        - Opening, Act I, Alternate title for "Waiting for the train," Box-Folder 45/1
        - Opening, Act I, scene 2, Alternate title for "Lady luck," Box-Folder 42/20
        - Opening, Act II
          - 13 parts (incomplete set) (Box-folder 43/11)
        - Our little captain
          - 17 parts (incomplete set) (Box-folder 43/12)
        - Overture
          - 18 parts (incomplete set) (Box-folder 43/13)
          - 12 band parts (incomplete set), Some parts have GG holograph emendations (Box-folder 44/1)
        - Play out
          - 12 parts (incomplete set) (Box-folder 44/2)
        - Sweet and low-down
          - 14 parts (incomplete set) (Box-folder 44/3)
          - 20 printed parts (incomplete set) (Box-folder 44/4)
        - Sweet and low-down. Insert
          - 10 parts (incomplete set) (Box-folder 44/5)
        - That certain feeling
          - 17 parts (incomplete set) (Box-folder 44/6)
          - 16 printed parts (incomplete set) (Box-folder 44/7)
        - These charming people
          - 17 parts (Box-folder 44/8)
        - Tip toes
          - 13 parts (incomplete set A) (Box-folder 44/9)
          - 9 parts (incomplete set B) (Box-folder 44/10)
        - Tip toes [variant]
          - Violin part only (Box-folder 44/11)
        - Waiting for the train
          - 16 parts (incomplete set) (Box-folder 45/1)
        - When do we dance?
          - 16 parts (incomplete set) (Box-folder 45/2)
          - 14 parts (incomplete set), 1st encore (Box-folder 45/3)
          - 10 parts (incomplete set), 2nd encore (Box-folder 45/4)
      - Instrumental part folders
        - 3 manuscripts, Piano part folders have notes in an unidentified hand; Laid in: Running list of songs (Box-folder 45/5)
      - Libretto
        - Typescript; [120] p., Emendations in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 45/6)
      - List of published songs
        - Photocopied typescript; [1] p. (Box-folder 45/7)
    - Top hole [1924] (Box 45)
      - Imagine me without my you
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p., Lyric in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 45/8)
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 45/8)
    - Treasure girl [1928] (Box 45-46)
      - According to Mr. Grimes
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 45/9)
      - A-hunting we will go!
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p., No lyric; Emendations in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 45/10)
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 45/10)
      - Dead men tell no tales
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [2] p. (Box-folder 45/11)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 45/11)
      - Feeling I'm falling
        - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p., No lyric (Box-folder 45/12)
        - GG holograph manuscript piano sketch; [1] p., Fragment of refrain; No lyric; In caption: No fooling, I'm falling (Box-folder 45/13)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 5 p., Emendations in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 45/14)
        - Copyist manuscript piano score; [2] p., Emendations in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 45/14)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 45/14)
      - Finale, Act I
        - Typescript lyric sheets; 4 p. (Box-folder 45/15)
      - Good-bye to the old love
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 45/16)
      - Good-bye to the old love, hello to the new, Alternate title for "Good-bye to the old love," Box-Folder 45/16
      - Got a rainbow
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Albert Sirmay; [4] p., Partial verse lyric in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 45/17)
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Albert Sirmay; 7 p., Lyric in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 45/17)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [4] p. (Box-folder 45/17)
      - Hunting motive
        - GG holograph manuscript melody line; [1] p. (Box-folder 45/18)
      - I don't think I'll fall in love today
        - 2 copyist manuscript piano-vocal scores; [4] p. ea., One has ukelele chords and emendations in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 45/19)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [4] p. (Box-folder 45/19)
      - I don't think I'll fall in love today. Encore
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 45/20)
      - I want to marry a marionette
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Albert Sirmay and GG; 1, 5 p., No lyric; Refrain melody chiefly in the hand of GG (Box-folder 46/1)
        - 2 copyist manuscript piano-vocal scores; 6 p. ea., One has emendations in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 46/2)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 46/2)
      - I've got a crush on you, See also "I've got a crush on you" from Strike up the band, Box-Folder 37/5-6
        - GG holograph manuscript lead sheet; [1] p., No lyric (Box-folder 46/3)
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 46/4)
      - I've got a rainbow, Alternate title for "Got a rainbow," Box-Folder 45/17
      - K-RA-ZY for you
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p., Emendations in the hand of Albert Sirmay (Box-folder 46/5)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 46/5)
      - Off with the old
        - Manuscript piano sketch; [3] p. (Box-folder 46/6)
      - Oh, so nice!
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p., Emendations in an unidentified hand (Box-folder 46/7)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 46/7)
        - 1st violin (4th stand) part (Box-folder 46/7)
        - Manuscript full score in the hand of William Daly; 6 p. (Box-folder 46/8)
        - Manuscript full score in the hand of William Daly; 11 p. (Box-folder 46/8)
      - Opening, Act I
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hands of Albert Sirmay and GG; 14 p., No lyric (Box-folder 46/9)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 16 p., No lyric (Box-folder 46/10)
      - Opening, Act I, scene 3, Alternate title for "Place in the country," Box-Folder 46/11
      - Opening, Act II, Alternate title for "Treasure island," Box-Folder 46/14
      - Place in the country
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Albert Sirmay; 16 p., No lyric (Box-folder 46/11)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 16 p. (Box-folder 46/11)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [5] p. (Box-folder 46/11)
      - Skull and bones
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 46/12)
      - Tally ho, Alternate title for "A-hunting we will go!," Box-Folder 45/10
      - This particular party
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 46/13)
      - Treasure Island
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 46/14)
      - What are we here for?
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 7 p., Emendations in the hand of Albert Sirmay (Box-folder 46/15)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 5 p., Emendations in the hand of Albert Sirmay (Box-folder 46/15)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 46/15)
      - What causes that?
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hands of Albert Sirmay and GG; [4] p., No lyric; Title and melody line of refrain in the hand of GG (Box-folder 46/16)
        - 2 copyist manuscript piano-vocal scores; 7 p. ea., No lyric (Box-folder 46/17)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [3] p. (Box-folder 46/17)
      - Where's the boy? Here's the girl!
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hands of Albert Sirmay and GG; [1, 5] p., No lyric; Title page and melody line of refrain in the hand of GG (Box-folder 46/18)
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Albert Sirmay; 7 p. (Box-folder 46/19)
        - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [5] p., No lyric (Box-folder 46/19)
        - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [8] p. (Box-folder 46/19)
    - Two little girls in blue [1921] (Box 46)
      - Dolly
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 46/20)
      - Dolly dear, Alternate title for "Dolly," Box-Folder 46/20
      - Finale, Act I, Alternate title for "We're off to India," Box-Folder 46/38
      - Finale, Act II
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 46/21)
      - Happy ending
        - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 46/22)